(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T02:14:16.638598",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
本日は「ホロライブ 5th Generation ライブ
Thank you very much for attending
Twinkle 4 You」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
"Hololive 5th Generation Live Twinkle 4 You" today.
ねぽらぼのおまるポルカです！
I'm Omaru Polka from NePoLaBo!
みんなおるかー？
Is everyone here?
おうるねー、
All right,
ポルカもおるかー？
is Polka here too?
おーりょー！
Ooryo!
そして、Live 4 ホロライブ5期生 獅白ぼたん です。
And for Live 4, Hololive 5th Generation's Shishiro Botan.
ライブを最後まで楽しんでいただくために、皆様へいくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live performance to the very end, we have a few announcements for you.
はい、まず初めに会場の皆様へご案内です。
First, an announcement for everyone in the venue.
本公演は声をだしての応援が可能です。
Cheering out loud is permitted during this performance.
ただし、周りの席の人に迷惑となるような大声を出す行為は
However, please cooperate by refraining from shouting
しないようにご協力をお願いいたします。
in a way that causes a nuisance to those in surrounding seats.
また、立ち上がっての応援も大歓迎です。ただし、
Standing up to cheer is also very welcome. However,
モッシュ、ダイブ等の危険行為は禁止とさせていただきます。
dangerous actions such as mosh pits and diving are prohibited.
ペンライトも大きく振り回して、周りの人の視界を遮ったり、
Please also be careful not to swing your penlights around too wildly,
ぶつかったりしないようにご注意ください。
blocking others' views or bumping into them.
また、指定の席からのご移動はしないようお願いいたします。
Also, please do not move from your assigned seats.
周囲のお客さまに配慮をした上で、思いっきり盛り上がっていきましょう！
Be considerate of the guests around you, and let's get hyped to the fullest!
本公演は避難誘導等の消灯を行います。万が一
Emergency lighting will be turned off during this show. In the unlikely
避難が必要になった場合はすぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、
event that evacuation becomes necessary, emergency lights will turn on immediately,
係員の指示に従っていただきますようお願いします。
so please follow the staff's instructions.
公演終了後は規制退場を行います。
After the performance ends, staggered exits will be implemented.
スタッフの指示があるまで、ご自分の席でお待ちください。
Please wait in your seats until instructed by staff.
また、イベント中気分が悪くなったり、何かあった場合は
Also, if you start feeling unwell or anything happens during the event,
早めに近くのスタッフにお知らせください。
please notify nearby staff as soon as possible.
場内での許可のない録音、撮影は禁止となっております。
Unauthorized recording and photography inside the venue are prohibited.
そのような行為を見つけた場合はご退場いただく場合がございます。
If such behavior is found, you may be asked to leave.
携帯電話やスマートフォンは音や振動を止めて見えないところにしまっておいてください。
Please turn off sounds and vibrations on mobile phones and smartphones and put them away out of sight.
そして本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入るため、お客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Also, since cameras for video streaming and photography will be inside the venue for this performance, audience members may appear on camera.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションや今後の活動に使用する可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了解ください。
Please understand in advance that these videos and photos may be used for promotions and future activities.
危険行為や禁止行為を見つけた場合、スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございます。
If dangerous or prohibited actions are spotted, staff may give you a warning.
ルールを守っていただけない場合には、安全確保のため公演を一時中断、もしくは中止となる可能性もございます。
If the rules are not followed, the performance may be temporarily suspended or canceled to ensure safety.
ルールをしっかり守って、みんなで楽しいライブにしましょう！
Please follow the rules strictly and let's all make it an enjoyable live show!
まもなく、配信でご覧の皆様への
Shortly, we will announce important notices
注意事項をお伝えします。
for those watching via stream.
最善の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、
We will prepare thoroughly to stream the live event,
生配信の特性上、回線の障害で映像の乱れや一時停止などが起こる可能性があります。
however, due to the nature of live streaming, line issues may cause video glitches or pauses.
あらかじめこちらご了解くださいませ。
Please understand this in advance.
そして、本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りしています。
Also, audio/video recording, mirroring, and illegal uploading of this live show are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です。
Instead, taking screenshots and posting them with images on SNS is warmly welcomed.
本公演のハッシュタグはハッシュタグ#ねぽらぼT4Uです。
The official hashtag for this performance is #NeporaboT4U.
ぜひハッシュタグを使ってライブを一緒に盛り上げててください。
Please use the hashtag to pump up the live performance together!
以上が開演前のご案内となります。ライブの開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
This concludes the pre-show announcement. Please wait a moment until the show begins.
一緒に盛り上がって楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's get hyped and enjoy it together!
一緒に盛り上がっていこう！
Let's get hyped together!
みんなのこと見てるからなー！
I'm watching all of you!
推しの曲めっちゃいいよね！
Your favorite idol's songs are just the best!
みるハコでチャンス！
Get the chance with Miruhako!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりでおしのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can fully enjoy your favorite content with immersive realism!
みるハコ最高！音も増やそう、みるハコ！
Miruhako is the best! Crank up the sound with Miruhako!
まもなく開演いたします。
The performance will start shortly.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: To All Attendees]
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Please beware of flashing lights during the production.]
公演終了後は規制退場を行います。
[Staggered exits will be held after the show.]
グッズラインナップ
[Goods Lineup]
ランダム 短冊風アクリルキーホルダー
[Random Strip Acrylic Keychains]
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ ホロライブプロダクションが、またまたカードに大集合！
Weiß Schwarz's Hololive Production makes another huge gathering on cards!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Expanding Weiss Schwarz!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol.2
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
推しの曲 めっちゃいいね！
My favorite's song is super good!
みるハコでチャンス！
A chance with Miruhaco!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
Enjoy your favorite's content with full realism via Miruhaco!
みるハコ最高！
Miruhaco is the best!
おうちも盛り上がろう、みるハコ！
Let's get hyped at home too with Miruhaco!
ホロライブ五期生ライブ Twinkle4Youにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for attending Hololive 5th Gen Live "Twinkle4You"!
こんねね！ホロライブ五期生オレンジ担当みんなの心のエネルギー・ドリンク桃鈴ねねです！
Konne! I'm Momosuzu Nene, the orange rep of Hololive 5th gen!
みなさんこいなみ！ホロライブ五期生の雪花ラミィです！
Hello everyone! I'm Lamy Yukihane of Hololive 5th gen!
ライブを最後まで楽しんでいただくために、皆さまへいくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live to the end, we have a few announcements.
まず初めに、会場の皆さまにご案内になります。
First of all, this is an announcement for everyone at the venue.
本公演は声を出しての応援がオッケーになっております。
Cheering with your voice is allowed in this performance.
ただし、周りの人の迷惑となるような大声を出す行為だけはしないようにご協力をお願いします。
However, please cooperate by not shouting loudly to bother others.
立ち上がっての応援も大歓迎です！
Cheering while standing up is also very welcome!
ただし、ライブ中のジャンプ等の危険行為は禁止とさせていただきます。
However, dangerous acts like jumping during the live are prohibited.
ペンライトも大きく振り回して周りの人の視界を遮ったりぶつかったりしないようご注意ください。
Be careful not to swing penlights widely to block others' view or hit them.
また指定の席からのご移動はないようにお願いします。
Also, please do not move from your assigned seat.
周囲のお客様に配慮した上で思い切り盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get hyped to the fullest while considering surrounding customers!
本公演は避難誘導等の消灯を行います。
Lights will be turned off for evacuation guidance during the show.
万が一避難が必要になった場合はすぐに非常灯が点灯しますので、係員の指示に従っていただけますようよろしくお願いします。
If evacuation is needed, emergency lights will turn on immediately; please follow staff instructions.
公演終了後は規制退場を行います。スタッフの指示があるまで自分の席で待っててね！
After the show, we will have regulated exits. Please wait in your seat until instructed!
また、このライブの中で気分が悪くなったり何かあった場合は早めに近くのスタッフさんに声をかけてください。
Also, if you feel unwell or need help during the live, please alert a staff member promptly.
場内での許可のない録音・撮影は禁止となっております。
Unauthorized recording and photography inside the venue are prohibited.
そのような行為を見つけた場合はご退場いただく場合がございます。
If such actions are found, you may be asked to leave.
携帯電話やスマートフォンは音や振動を止めて見えないところにしまっておいてください。
Please silence mobile phones and smartphones and store them out of sight.
本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入るため、お客様の様子が映り込んじゃう場合があります。
Cameras for streaming and photos will be present, so customers' appearances may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションや今後の活動に使用する可能性が、大体大体大体になっておりますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
These may be used for promotions or future activities... so please understand in advance.
嫌な人は顔を隠すの！
If you don't like it, cover your face!
危険行為や禁止行為を見つけた場合はスタッフが注意させていただく場合がございます。
If dangerous or prohibited acts are found, staff may give you a warning.
ルールを守っていただけない場合には安全確保のため公演を一時中断、もしくは中止となる可能性もございます。
If rules aren't followed, the performance may be temporarily suspended or canceled for safety.
ルールをしっかり守って、みんなで楽しいライブにしましょう！
Let's all follow the rules and have a fun live together!
続いて、配信の皆さまに注意事項をお伝えいたします。
Next, we have important notices for everyone watching the stream.
万全の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、生配信の特性上、不慮の障害で映像の乱れや一時停止等が起こる可能性があります。
We will prepare thoroughly, but due to live streaming nature, unexpected video glitches or pauses may occur.
あらかじめご了承いただいた上で、本ライブの録音、録画やミラー配信、違法アップロードは固くお断りしております、駄目です！
Please understand this; recording, mirror streaming, or illegal uploading of this live is strictly prohibited—no!
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して画像とともにSNSにご投稿いただくことは大歓迎です！
Instead, taking screenshots and posting them on SNS along with the image is very welcome!
本公演のハッシュタグはハッシュタグ #ねぽらぼT4U です！
The hashtag for this performance is #neporaboT4U!
ぜひハッシュタグを使ってライブを一緒に盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag and liven up the live together!
以上が、開演前のご案内となります。ライブの開演までもうすぐです。今しばらくお待ちください。
That concludes pre-show announcements. The show is about to start; please wait a moment.
一緒にライブ盛り上がっていこう！みんなでいっぱい盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's get hyped for the live together! Let's get super hyped everyone!
みんなー、おー！
Everyone, oh!
もう少し待っててねー
Please wait just a little longer!
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the newborn excitement echo out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
きらめきにのって
Riding on the sparkle!
覚えているかな 最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
懐かしいね 私たちの声が 震えていた
It brings back memories, our voices trembling back then.
本当は少し
Truth is, we were a little...
あの日から続く 未来は みんなとつかんだ
The future continuing from that day, grasped together with everyone,
宝物よ もっと もっと もっともっと
is our treasure! Faster, faster, faster and faster,
加速するハート 一緒に行くよ どこまでも
our accelerating hearts will go together anywhere!
アイレディ 準備はOK?
Ready? Is preparation OK?
開け 夢の扉を キラめききらいた
Open the door to our dreams, sparkling bright!
生まれ立てのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the newborn excitement echo out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me.
君に愛しくって やってきたんだ みんなで歌を
I came to you with so much love, let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ キラめきまとって
An endless melody, wrapped in sparkles!
1曲ね もっともっと 盛り上がっていこう
Let's get even more hyped up for this song!
届いてるかな 私の声
Is my voice reaching you?
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you,
そのスマイル 理想の音色に 悔しくって
that smile towards our ideal tone, even when frustrated,
みんなと泣き笑ったね
we cried and laughed together.
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと すべて抱きしめて
Hugging everything tight, tight, tight, tight,
一緒に行こう どこまでも
let's go together anywhere!
アイレディ 準備はOK?
Ready? Is preparation OK?
進め 希望の道を
Advance along the path of hope!
キラめききらいた 好きな気持ち カラフルに奏でたいな
Sparkling bright, I want to play my favorite feelings colorfully!
最高の場所 最高のみんなと
At the best place, with everyone the best,
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not an illusion!
君の心が 幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed in happiness,
重ねていくハーモニー キラめきまとって
Layering harmonies, wrapped in sparkles,
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing!
そんな願いやわがまも いいでしょ?
Such wishes and selfishness are fine, right?
はじめようか さあ diving
Let's start, now diving,
待ってても意味ない timing
Waiting around has no meaning, it's all about timing.
あの魚みたいに swimming swimming
Swimming, swimming like those fish.
引き寄せるの lighting
The lighting draws us in closer.
まだ見えないよ maybe
Maybe it's still out of sight,
この先には何があるの？
Wondering what lies beyond this point?
まだ早いよ take it
It's too early, just take it,
追い付くまで shaking
Shaking until we catch up.
でもたまに止まってさ thinking thinking
But sometimes, stopping to think, thinking,
変えてみせる change
Let's try to change it up!
踏み出すのかな stepping
Are we stepping forward?
つかんでみるよ キラキラ my dream
Let's grasp that sparkling dream of ours!
叶う日まで story 繋ぐから
Connecting the story until the day it comes true,
だって君に ずっと見ていてほしいから
Because I want you to always watch me!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Just being happy, having fun, and feeling loved isn't enough...
今も今もあるけど
Even now, even now, worries are still there, but...
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
I'm here, I'm right here!
君と同じ世界を 見つめて
Gazing at a world just like yours,
キラメキライトあびて
Sparkling and glowing bright!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Feel the heartbeat of a brand new day, letting it echo!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best companions,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
Finding where we belong because you found me!
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みみとぶ！
I came here just because I wanted to see you!
終わらないメロディ キラメキにのって
An endless melody, glowing with brilliance,
キラメキままとって イエイ！
Shining brighter and brighter!
みんな 2曲目からも飛ばしていくぞ！
Let's blow past the second track and beyond!
ありがとう！今日は楽しんでいってね！
Thank you! Enjoy the rest of the show!
どこまでも踏み出そう
Let's keep going, stepping forward no matter how far,
銀河の真ん中 笑い合って
Laughing together in the middle of the Milky Way!
Wonderful tour!
みんな ペンライトもっともっと見せて！
Everyone, show us that Penlight glow once more!
一歩目が遠くに行くか
The first step is already far ahead,
キラリ むずに入り込まれた
Sparkling and crying with pure emotion,
違うよ 出会いたくて
It's different because I wanted to meet you.
ほら みんな ここにいる
Look, everyone is right here!
夢の夜でだけどね
A dream-like night, but you know,
ファンタジーじゃない予感
It's more than just a fantasy!
優勢群 負けないよ
United together, we won't lose!
光 放って
Letting our light shine free!
どんなどこでも飛び越えて
Leaping over any obstacle whatsoever,
銀河の真ん中 更新しよう
Let's update the middle of the Milky Way!
キラメキの搾りかす あとだって
Leaving our footprints in the juice of starlight,
もしも 新しくなる
Even if a new universe is born,
ワンツースリーイエイ！ 激チリばめ
One, two, three, yeah! Scattering everywhere!
ワンツースリーイエイ！ 生マンゴー電を
One, two, three, yeah! Calling out your name!
ワンツースリーイエイ！ 旅していく季節が
One, two, three, yeah! As seasons keep passing by,
今 始まったんだよ きっと
It's finally begun now, for sure!
Wonderful tour!
ボクらの 心はいつも
Our hearts are always burning bright,
燃えてるんだ 個性なのよ
Burning with individual colors!
だからね 手を繋いだら
That's why, when we hold hands,
生まれるものがある
Something new is born!
それは 新しい宇宙 君と描く明日
That's a brand new universe you and I will map out,
仲間集めて 世界を作ろう
Gathering our friends to create a world!
気づいてみたら ボケのまた棚が
If you notice, there's another galaxy,
星の海は渡って
Crossing across a sea of stars,
Sparkle days!
どこまでも踏み出そう
Let's keep going, stepping forward no matter how far,
青春を書き分けて 無限の空だ待ってるよ
Dividing up our youth, waiting for an endless sword!
準備 OK さあ輝たへ
Preparation OK, let's shine bright!
輝きは止まらない
Our brilliance still won't stop,
銀河の真ん中 姿勢がない
Because we can't hide our attitude in the middle of the Milky Way!
君とならいけるから 願いの向こう 未来へと
If it's with you, we can do it, so let's reach beyond our wishes!
ワンツースリーイエイ！ 激チリばめ
One, two, three, yeah! Scattering everywhere!
ワンツースリーイエイ！ 生マンゴー電を
One, two, three, yeah! Calling out your name!
ワンツースリーイエイ！ 旅していく季節が
One, two, three, yeah! As seasons keep passing by,
今 始まったんだよ きっと
It's finally begun now, for sure!
so let’s go！どこまでも 踏み出そう
So let's go! Let's step out everywhere,
銀河のまんなか 笑い合って
laughing together in the galaxy,
wonderful tour！
wonderful tour!
1, 2, 3… yeah！
1, 2, 3... yeah!
奇跡散りばめ
Miracles scatter,
1, 2, 3… yeah！
1, 2, 3... yeah!
何万光年を
Tens of thousands of light-years,
1, 2, 3… yeah！
1, 2, 3... yeah!
旅してゆく季節が 今 始まったんだよ きっと！
The season of journeying has surely begun right now!
wonderful tour！
wonderful tour!
届いたかなー？
Did it reach you?
お待たせー！
Thanks for waiting!
えへへ、みんな！
Hehe, everyone!
５期生にとっての初めてのライブ、やっとできたねー！
Our very first 5th Gen live, we finally did it!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ていうことで、自己紹介をしましょうか！
So, let's do self-introductions!
じゃあ、ねぽらぼの…あ、ね、れ、れ、れ！あははは！
So, Nepolabo's... ah, ne, re, re, re! Ahahaha!
ペンライト、オレンジ、オレンジね！めちゃ綺麗！
Penlights, orange, orange! So pretty!
お、オレンジだ！すごい！
Oh, it's orange! Amazing!
ネネが「みんなの心は？」って聞いたら、みんなは？
When Nene asks 'What is everyone's heart?', what do you say?
エナジードリンク！
Energy drink!
エナジードリンクだね、みんな！
Energy drink, everyone!
はいライブ、ごきげんオレンジ担当とみんなの心の…
Yes, live, cheerful orange rep and everyone's heart's...
エナジードリンク！
Energy drink!
ももすずねねです！いえーい！
Momosuzu Nene! Yay!
はい、ポルカおるかオルよ、ホロライブごきげんおまるポルカです！
Yes, Polka oru ka oru yo, Hololive cheerful Omaru Polka!
みんなどうやらオルらに力を貸してくれっていう感じだ。
It seems everyone is willing to lend us your power.
まだね、すべてを解放してなかったから。
Because we hadn't released everything yet.
みんな「ポルカおるか？」って聞いてくれるかな？
Can everyone ask 'Is Polka here?'
「ポルカおるかー？」ってね！いくよ！
Saying 'Is Polka hereー?' Let's go!
せーの！ポルカおるかー！
Ready, go! Is Polka hereー!
おんじょー！ホロライブごきげんおまるポルカです、今日はよろしくー！
Got it! Hololive cheerful Omaru Polka, nice to meet you todayー!
みんなわかってるよね？
Everyone knows, right?
ロミって言ったらみんなの？
If I say Lamy, everyone's...?
あーわかってる！じゃあ愛してるのは？って言ったら
Ah, you know! Then if I say 'Who do you love?'
ということで改めまして、え、ラミィちゃんしか！
So once again, um, only Lamy-chan!
あいしてるー！
I love youー!
あいしてるのは？ロミィちゃんだよー！
Who do you love? Lamy-chan!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい、ししろんはいつも通りね、シンプルに行きますんで。
Yes, Botan will be simple as usual, going plainly.
ラライオン！
Lalaion!
ホロライブごきげんししろんボタンです！
Hololive cheerful Shishiro Botan!
あ、すいません。それ、私が作った挨拶なんですけど、3年間ずっと使ってる…
Ah, sorry. That's a greeting I made, and I've been using it for 3 years...
ラライオンのこと、後でやっていただきます。
You'll do the 'Lalaion' thing later.
わかった、わかった！あとでDMするね。
Got it, got it! I'll DM you later.
はい、ではえ、みんな！
Yes, then um, everyone!
ライブといえば？お！何？ヘビ？
Speaking of live? Oh! What? Snake?
ウェーブ！ウェーブだよ！
Wave! It's wave!
やりたいでしょ？やりたいよね？
You want to do it, right? You want to, right?
オレンジ上手ウェーブいきまーす！
Orange stage-right wave, here we go!
ねねが走りすぎたらこうやって上げて下げてね。
When Nene runs too much, raise and lower like this.
いくよ！せーの！ねころんさいとー！
Here we go! Ready, go! Neko-ron-siteー!
ということで、みんな高速切り替えすごい！
With that, everyone's high-speed switching is amazing!
次はね、次のみんなも走り去りますんで皆さんよろしくお願いしますね。
Next up, the next group will also be running by, so please cheer them on!
愛せないって取りすぎるかね、のこと。
"Can't help but love them too much"? What a thing to say.
ふたりちゃん、聞いて。
Futari-chan, listen to this.
もっと早くしよう。愛したい。
Let's go faster. I want to love them.
愛してるのふたりちゃん。
I love you, Futari-chan.
よし、ししろん、全員、やろうやろう。
Alright, Shishiro, everyone, let's do it.
みんな、お疲れ様。
Everyone, good work.
普段、私がさ、私も愛してるとやりたいの。
Usually, I want to say "I love you" too.
普段、やんないもん。
You don't usually do that!
え！？ししろんしか愛せないの？
Eh?! You can only love Shishiro?
愛せない。うん。
Can't love anyone else. Yeah.
ああ、じゃあししろんから行きます。
Ah, then Shishiro will go first.
めちゃめちゃ早く行くからね。めちゃめちゃ早く、めちゃめちゃ早く！
I'm going really fast. Really fast, super fast!
いいよいいよ。ししろんしか愛せない！
It's fine, it's fine. I can only love Shishiro!
ししろんさん、そんなに早くないです。
Shishiro-san, that wasn't very fast.
え、早くなかった？
Eh, wasn't it fast?
もっと、もっといける？もっといける？
Can you go faster? Can you go faster?
早いか！クラウチングスタート。
Fast! Crouching start.
いや、でも、ししろん、ししろんしか愛せない！
No, but, Shishiro, I can only love Shishiro!
ししろん最速おまけ行きます。
Shishiro's fastest bonus coming up.
ああ、じゃあポルカだね、マシット、マシットね。
Ah, then it's Polka, mashitto, mashitto.
ポルカは何でなの？ポルカ、オルカでしょ。
Why Polka? Polka, Orca, right?
あの、ポルカは普通にわーで行くから、ポルカがね、ここで一番最後に手本を見せるっていうわけ。
Um, Polka normally goes "waa!", so Polka will show the example last here.
でね、皆さんまずペンライトを赤、ありがとうございます。こちらはですね、まず皆さんね、あの、お手元の腕を降ろしていただいてから始めましょうか。
And then, everyone, first, pen lights red, thank you very much. For this, let's start after everyone lowers your arms at hand.
じゃあ、ポルカはこっち走り去って行くから、そのポルカが来るタイミングで上げるんだよ。
Then, Polka will run off this way, so raise it at the timing Polka comes.
せーの！わー！
Ready, go! Waa!
はい、完璧！みんな拍手！
Yes, perfection! Everyone, applause!
自分に拍手！隣の人にも拍手して！
Applause for yourself! Applause for the person next to you too!
じゃあちょっと、なんか満足しちゃったよね。
Well, somehow we got satisfied, didn't we?
ちょっとね、みんなスタートだからお水飲んでな。
A bit, everyone is at the start so drink water.
まあ言うて、あの、ライブだからね、ちょっと歌もほら、歌わないとな。
Well, since it's a live, you know, we gotta sing songs too.
あ、そうなんだ、あそうなの。
Ah, is that so, ah, I see.
あ、すいません、すいません。忘れてました。失礼します。
Ah, sorry, sorry. I forgot. Excuse me.
みなさまにちょっとお知らせなんですけど、
An announcement for everyone,
えー、しらみせの方、あ、次の曲までね！
Uh, Shiramise, ah, until the next song!
最後まで見たい人は、ぜひ、あの、概要欄をチェックしてくださいっていうお知らせでした。
That was an announcement to definitely check the description if you want to watch until the end.
ま、配信に向けてのお知らせです。現地はどれだけ盛り上がってるか、ちょっと大きな元気な声を聞かせてもらえるかな？
Well, that's an announcement for the stream. Can we hear how excited the venue is with some big, energetic voices?
どうだい？イェーイ！
How is it? Yay!
さあ、これを聴くとね、きっともほら盛り上がって
Now, when you listen to this, you'll surely get even more excited...
さあ、ばけたいほど盛り上がっておりますが、次の曲は、じゃあめちゃくちゃ盛り上げていこうぜ、ねえねえ。
Now, we're extremely hyped up, but for the next song, let's hype it up like crazy, hey hey.
反対してる場合ちゃうで。あのね、私らのパート最後だから思いっきり盛り上げていきましょう！
This isn't the time to be opposed. You know, since our part is the last, let's hype it up to the fullest!
最初は、え、ねねポルがメインで歌うから、しらみがダンスで参加してもらいまーす。
First, uh, Nene and Polka will sing mainly, so Lamy will participate with dancing.
じゃあ、ねねちゃん行ってくれるかな？
Well, Nene-chan, can you go?
はい！それでは早速次の曲、聞いてください！せーの、レッドゾーン突入！
Yes! Then please listen to the next song right away! Ready, go! Red zone entry!
便利屋に依頼をしたなら (Hi!Hi!Hi!Let's go!)
If you hired the odd-job agency (Hi! Hi! Hi! Let's go!)
あとは任せていいのよ (大船にね 乗ったつもりで)
Leave the rest to us (As if boarding a large ship)
方法も手段も手口も (Hi!Hi!Hi!Let's go!)
Methods, means, and tactics (Hi! Hi! Hi! Let's go!)
すべて委ねて頂戴 (なんとしてでも やり遂げるわ)
Entrust everything to us (We'll pull it off no matter what)
強行突入 銃撃砲撃
Forced entry, gunfire and bombardment,
爆弾もセット完了
bombs are also set and ready.
さあゆこう 誇り胸に今
Now let's go, with pride in our hearts!
最高も最低も 味わって 乗り越えて
Experiencing both the best and the worst, overcoming them,
大切なのは信頼だって 信じているから 譲れない
what matters most is trust, and since we believe in it, we won't yield.
我らアウトロー 社員一同
We are outlaws, all employees together,
どこまでも 進むわよ
advancing no matter where we go.
便利屋はいつも本気よ 要求通りの成果を
The odd-job agency is always serious, delivering results just as requested,
これでもかと出してみせる
and showing off with flair!
ハードボールドな毎日
A hard-boiled everyday life,
くふふ~ 楽しい未来を まちがいなく実現する
humming along, making a joyful future a reality without fail.
やりたい放題 用意は周到 進むわよ この覇道
Doing whatever we want with careful preparation, advancing down this supremacy road,
誰にも邪魔させない そうよ
we won't let anyone get in our way!
成功も失敗も 貴重な経験ね
Success and failure are both precious experiences.
勝負が決まる瞬間まで 絶対決意は曲げない
Until the moment the outcome is decided, we will never bend our resolve.
我らパートナー 力あわせて
We are partners, combining our strength,
何度でも 挑むわよ
challenging over and over again!
ピンチの時も 涙の夜も 支えてくれたから
Because you supported me through pinches and tearful nights,
さあゆこう 絆胸に今
now let's go, with bonds in our hearts!
最高も最低も 味わって 乗り越えて
Experiencing both the best and the worst, overcoming them,
大切なのは信頼だって 信じているから 譲れない
what matters most is trust, and since we believe in it, we won't yield.
我らアウトロー 社員一同
We are outlaws, all employees together.
劣等上等 BRING IT ON
Bring it on!
列島上々 不眠日本
子供騙しのマゼマティカ
Machinations to fool the kids,
ご立派 警鐘 気取りでん
A grand alarm, get a clue!
高みの見物ばかりじゃつまんですね
Just watching from above gets boring,
ほらもっと
Right back up!
間間違って上等
Getting it wrong and rising up,
退屈に手をかけて
Reaching out to boredom,
こんなところじゃ終われない
We won't end it in a place like this.
ぬくぬく気が触れそう泣き虫ぴえん
It's slipping away, making my spirit itch.
ごっこ遊びも芝居もさよなら
Farewell to rough-and-tumble play and farce,
ダダダダ あたし大人になる
Da-da-da, we're gonna grow up.
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Tasting both the sour and the sweet right now.
パパパパ 変わる時代
Pa-pa-pa, changing times,
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょ
It's not just about bad things, you know.
過去も、罪も、罰も、すべて
The past, sins, punishments, and all—
素手で、愛で 生き抜いてやり返すわ
With bare hands and love, we'll survive and live it down!
yeah 挑発 あたし達はno doubt
Yeah, provocation, we're no doubt!
緑のアイツにばっか構ってんね
Always messing with those green guys, huh?
さあburn up いつになったら貰える合格
Come on, burn up, when do we get a passing grade?
赤ペンいれてよ どこがダメなんですか
Put in some red ink, what's wrong with that?
酒女金ドラッグ やっちゃってコンプレックス
Girls, booze, money, drugs, messing up with complexes.
チルっちaiight... 冗談じゃんブラックジョーク
Chill out, aiight? No joke, black joke.
中指立てたくなような事情さ
Situations that make you wanna raise your middle finger—
ありすぎて指が足りねえからhands up and what's up
There's so many, I don't have enough fingers, so hands up and what's up!
最低? もともとだろbring it on
The absolute lowest? From the very start, bring it on!
「まあまあ」なんか要らない
"Now, now," we don't need any of that.
欲しがります死ぬまでは
We'll be greedy until the day we die.
伸びた背中 育った街に投げキッス
With straightened back, we blow a kiss to the town we grew up in.
見せ場はこっから 覚悟しとけよ
The show starts from here, so get ready!
ダダダダ 僕ら大人になる
Da-da-da, we're gonna grow up.
カウンター狙い 最低な日々に
Aiming for the counters, on the lowest days,
然々と噛ます一撃
A piercing blow dealt with poise.
誰も読めない先まだあいこでしょ
An unknown future where nobody can read ahead.
素手で、生きて! 生き抜いて覆すよ
With bare hands, live! Survive and rewrite it!
くだらないことばかりが譲れない
We can't yield to things that aren't even cool.
わかるかあたしの美学
Do you understand? That's our aesthetic.
この馬鹿正直な拳ひとつが一途なんですの
This foolish, straightforward punch is just single-minded.
切り札
A losing hand.
愚直なんですの
Just being foolish.
がなる劣等 一抜けろさらば!
Such inferiority, break through and say goodbye!
ダダダダ あたし大人になる
Da-da-da, we're gonna grow up.
酸いも甘いも噛み分けて今
Tasting both the sour and the sweet right now.
燦々 交わるミライも
Brilliantly intersecting milieus.
もう子供じゃないのわかるでしょう
You know we're not kids anymore, right?
ダダダダあたし大人になる
Da-da-da, we're gonna grow up.
カウンター狙い 最低な日々に
Aiming for the counters, on the lowest days,
スイも甘いも髪は染めていな
Water tastes sweet, and mom's hair is dyed,
散々交わるミライも
A future where we intertwine.
ことも雑魚も散々いの分かるでしょう
Even if we stumble, we know the way!
いたい いたい 待って くれたい
Wait, stay, give me a break!
素手で、住んで生き抜いてちょうどだわ
With bare hands, live! Survive and let's go!
それでは皆様お先にバイカジ
So everyone, let's buy in advance!
フロアがわき上がりました
The floor... just popped out!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!